[
  {
    "question": "How old your elder brother was 10 years before you was born, mate?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "title": "10 years"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "title": "11 years"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "title": "12 years"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "title": "14 years"
      }
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [1]
  },
  {
    "question": "2 + 2 = ?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "title": "3"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "title": "6"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "title": "5"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "title": "4"
      }
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [4]
  },
  {
    "question": "4-letters words",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "title": "Game"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "title": "Task"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "title": "Millionaire"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "title": "Border"
      }
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [1, 2]
  },
  {
    "question": "10 / 2 = ?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "title": "2"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "title": "1"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "title": "5"
      }
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [3]
  },
  {
    "question": "10 + 3 = ?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "title": "13"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "title": "11"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "title": "7 + 6"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "title": "7"
      }
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [1, 3]
  },
  {
    "question": "10 - 7 = ?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "title": "13"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "title": "11"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "title": "3"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "title": "7"
      }
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [3]
  },
  {
    "question": "Capital of Great Britain?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "title": "Kyiv"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "title": "Manchester"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "title": "New York"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "title": "London"
      }
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [4]
  },
  {
    "question": "1 + 3 = ?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "title": "2 + 2"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "title": "3 + 1"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "title": "4"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "title": "4 + 0"
      }
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [1, 2, 3, 4]
  },
  {
    "question": "The bravest country of the world?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "title": "The USA"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "title": "Great Britain"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "title": "Poland"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "title": "Ukraine"
      }
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [4]
  },
  {
    "question": "What sport play footballers?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "title": "Baseball"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "title": "Basketball"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "title": "Skating"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "title": "Football"
      }
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [4]
  },
  {
    "question": "The most valuable person in Ukraine?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "title": "President Zelenskiy"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "title": "Arestovich"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "title": "Kim"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "title": "Povoroznyuk"
      }
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [1]
  },
  {
    "question": "The capital of the greatest country of the world?",
    "possibleAnswers": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "title": "Ottava"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "title": "Praha"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "title": "Washington"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "title": "Kyiv"
      }
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [4]
  }
]
